<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 22:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Regression Project, Part -1, Data Preprocessing</title>
      <link>/post/regression-project-part-1-data-preprocessing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/regression-project-part-1-data-preprocessing/</guid>
      <description>Main IdeaThe idea of this new series of data is to understand more obout different types of regressiion and how they works.
Regression, is to find a relationship between dependant variable and independent variablewhat kind of relationship exists.How Much each Indipendent variblee affect the dependent variableThe few Regressions that we are going to work in this series are givven below1. Simple Linear Regression2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Movie and TV Show Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/post/netflix-movie-and-tv-show-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/netflix-movie-and-tv-show-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Important Findings:It will take 283 days from now to watch all available Movies in Netflix
4 in 10, Movies or TV Shows are not suitable for childrens under 17
67% of TV Shows never made to Second Season.
Only 6% TV Shows have more than 5 Seasons
Netflix and Chill, That famous saying, So netflix has entertaining us for almost a decade now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whatsapp Chat Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/post/checking-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/checking-post/</guid>
      <description>AboutThe Whole Idea about this analysis, is to Understand about the persons chatting behavior and finding pattern in Whatsapp Messaging
In this we will be analysing the chat between two persons
From the below chart we can clearly see the number of messages sent each day
The Total number of messages were : 5733 
Number of messages sent by each persons:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Engineer By Degree, Data Analyst by heart.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>